{
  "title": "Assessment: Living and Nonliving Things",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which cannot be done by humans?",
      "choices": ["Grow", "Reproduce", "Swim", "Fly"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "A tadpole can _____ into an adult frog.",
      "choices": ["Grow", "Reproduce", "Move", "Run"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "It is when you react to something that happens.",
      "choices": ["Happy", "Respond", "Grow", "Sad"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "These are the soft coverings of a bird's body.",
      "choices": ["Skin", "Scales", "Beak", "Feather"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which object is not made out of wood?",
      "choices": ["Table", "Chair", "Soil", "House"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "It is used to create clothes and dresses.",
      "choices": ["Stone", "Silk", "Water", "Leaves"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Living things don't need to drink water.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Living things can reproduce and make babies.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Non-living things can sense and respond to their environment.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Plants are an example of non-living things.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    }
  ]
}
